Finding Aid for Paul Bigby papers, 1937-1998
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Paul Bigby papers 1937-1998
Bigby, Paul.
1.5 linear feet
8857 Aa 2
Alumnus of the University of Michigan, active in the University's Alumni Association and the University of Michigan Detroit Club; alumni activity files.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of Paul Bigby (donor no. 6505 ).
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Paul Bigby was a graduate of the University of Michigan College of Engineering, class of 1931. Following graduation, Bigby continued to be involved in University alumni activities.
The collection consists almost entirely of topical files, correspondence, and programs relating to his University of Michigan alumni activities, especially the Football Bust and U-M Night.
Subjects:
University of Michigan--Alumni and alumnae.; University of Michigan. Alumni Association.; Bigby, Paul.; China--History--1976-2002.
- University of Michigan alumni activities, 1937-1972
  - Alumni Association
    - Minutes and reports, 1946-1949, 3 folders (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1946-1948, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Constitution Revision Committee
    - Constitution and bylaws (1897-1968) (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1970, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Football Bust, 1946-1972 (scattered dates), 12 folders (Box 1)
  - Football Clinic, 1945 (Box 1)
  - U of M Nights, 1943-1949 (scattered dates) (Box 1)
- U-M Engineering Class of 1931
  - Reunion files, 1937-1985 (scattered dates), 17 folders (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1941-1986, 16 folders (Box 1)
  - Memorial Fund (scattered dates), 8 folders (Box 1)
  - Mailings, 1980-1993 (scattered dates) (Box 1)
- Other Materials
  - Correspondence with friend in Peoples Republic of China, 1978-1995, 6 folders (Box 2)
  - Memoirs of Grace Bigby, 1998 (Box 2)
  - Excerpts from Memoirs (Box 2)